Faculty Women's Club. Newsletters. 1930-2000.
UCLA Library Special Collections
Faculty Women's Club. Newsletters.
1930-2000
University Archives Record Series 693
UCLA Library Special Collections
1.2 linear ft. (3 boxes)
Record Series 693 contains newsletters generated by UCLA's Faculty Women's Club from 1930-2000.
Faculty Women's Club.
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
Scope and Content
Record Series 693 contains newsletters generated by UCLA's Faculty Women's Club from 1930-2000.
This is an active record series; additional University records are expected to be added.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 4475133
- Newsletters., 1930-1931. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  General note
  Nov, May.
- Newsletters., 1931-1933. (Box 1, Folders 2-3)
  All.
- Newsletters., 1933-1934. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Oct, Dec.
- Newsletters., 1934-1940. (Box 1, Folders 5-10)
- Newsletters., 1940-1941. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  No Jan.
- Newsletters., 1941-1943. (Box 1, Folders 12-13)
- Newsletters., 1943-1944. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Oct, May.
- Newsletters., 1944-1945. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  No Oct.
- Newsletters., 1945-1946. (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Newsletters., 1946-1947. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  No May.
- Newsletters., 1947-1955. (Box 1, Folders 18-25)
- Newsletters., 1955-1956. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  No Apr.
- Newsletters., 1956-1962. (Box 1, Folders 27-32)
- Newsletters., 1962-1979. (Box 2, Folders 1-17)
- Newsletters., 1979-1980. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  No Nov/Dec.
- Newsletters., 1980-1988. (Box 2, Folders 19-26)
- Newsletters., 1988-1989. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Newsletters., 1989-1990. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  May/June.
- Newsletters., 1990-1994. (Box 3, Folders 3-6)
- Newsletters., 1994-1995. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Newsletters., 1995-1996. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Oct.
- Newsletters., 1996-2000. (Box 3, Folders 9-12)